nusphere.com 2016-05-14

# Your Privacy: NuSphere Corporation

Privacy Policy

Last update: Monday, October 04, 2004

We at NuSphere Corporation ("NuSphere") are constantly striving to provide excellent service to you, our customers and business partners, while building a long-lasting relationship with you. To achieve these goals, we occasionally need information about you when you visit our site.

When you visit NuSphere.com, you may be providing NuSphere with information about your visit on two levels: 

  * Statistics collected as you browse our Web site. 
  * Organizational and personal information you knowingly give us. 

Because NuSphere respects your right to privacy, we want you to be aware of how we handle this information.

Our Commitment to Your Privacy

NuSphere assures you that we do not 

  * Sell the names and addresses of our customers [site users] to outside vendors. 

NuSphere does: 

  * Safeguard customers' information from unauthorized access. 
  * Collect, maintain and use customer information as necessary to provide the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet customer's needs (e.g. customer care or new products or services). 
  * Honor customers' requests to remove their names from our telephone or mail solicitation lists in a timely manner. Just [Contact Us](http://shop.nusphere.com/contact_us/). 
  * Maintain confidentiality of customer information when undertaking projects with other companies. 

NuSphere has always valued your privacy, and we reinforce this belief throughout our organization. Your information will be protected as described unless the specific Web page says otherwise. If you have further questions about our Privacy Policy, please [Contact Us](http://shop.nusphere.com/contact_us/).

__Information this Site Gathers/Tracks__

Statistics Collected as You Browse Our Web Sites

As you browse the site, NuSphere's Web servers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. Via Web server logs, we monitor statistics such as: 

  * How many people visit our Web site. 
  * Which pages people visit on our Web site. 
  * From which domains our visitors come (e.g., "yahoo.com" or "aol.com"). 
  * Which browsers people use to visit our Web site. 

While we gather this information, none of it is associated with you as an individual. We use these statistics to improve our Web site, to monitor its performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use.

Organizational and Personal Information You Knowingly Give Us

Within www.NuSphere.com, you may be asked to give us personal or organizational information in order to receive information about a product or service. This information may range from your generic zip code, to your specific phone number, product serial number, control codes, account number, credit card number, e-mail address, organization, URL or mailing address.

__Use of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks__

Your IP Address and Host Name 

NuSphere's Web site logs Host Names (or IP addresses when the Host Name is not available) for systems administration and security purposes. These logs are monitored and analyzed to maintain systems and information security and allow us to constantly improve the value and the availability of the Web content.

Registration Forms

We encourage all visitors to register with NuSphere.com, although registration is not required, except for access to our premium content areas. The registration forms require users to give us accurate contact information (like name and email address) and references that help us better serve you. Your name and email address may be used to send you information about our company, product updates, special offers, and newsletters. To opt out of receiving communications from NuSphere, please [Contact Us](http://shop.nusphere.com/contact_us/).

_Order Forms and Enrollment Forms_

Our order forms securely collect visitor's contact information and financial information (like your credit card number and other billing information). Contact information on the order form is used for order fulfillment and may be shared with our Partners or Resellers if that is necessary to fulfill your request. The information that we require in our order form is only used to process your order quickly and accurately. Your contact information will only be used to send you the product that you purchase and your billing information will only be used to bill you for that product. During the purchasing process, you may be given the opportunity to sign up for future e-mailings regarding our products, services, and promotions. If you sign up, NuSphere will share your contact information with other NuSphere partner companies only, not with other outside companies.

As NuSphere's online systems become more sophisticated, you may also be given the option of registering a profile with NuSphere. This would store your name, purchase history, and billing information to make it easier for you to shop and purchase products/services from us in the future. Once profiling is available, you may opt out of this feature at any time by changing/canceling your profile online.

Cookies

A cookie is a small, encrypted data string our server writes to your hard drive that contains your unique NuSphere User ID. We use cookies to deliver Web content specific to your interests and to control access to NuSphere premium content. A cookie cannot be used to access or otherwise compromise the data on your hard drive. You can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies if you do not want us to establish and maintain a unique NuSphere User ID. Please be aware that cookies may be required to complete certain functions on NuSphere.com.

__Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks__

The information you submit may be shared with third parties if it is necessary to complete your request, provide you with access to downloadable software, or as required by law.

Information Security

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. When you place an order, the information is encrypted using the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Links to Other Sites

The NuSphere Web sites contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these other sites.

Opt-out Policy and Procedure

Our site provides users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our Partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. Additionally, visitors who wish to remove their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service can [Contact Us](http://shop.nusphere.com/contact_us/).

Correcting/Update Policy

If you would like to correct and/or update your information, please [Contact Us](http://shop.nusphere.com/contact_us/).

Oversight

If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please [Contact Us](http://shop.nusphere.com/contact_us/). We will address any issue to the best of our abilities.

Changes to Policy

NuSphere will occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy policy.
